American Vaudeville Museum collection, 1850s-2007 (bulk 1910s-1940s)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IV: Performers, 4.75 linear foot
  - Performers Bi - Bu
    - Blake, Eubie (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Blake, Robert (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Blesh, Rudi (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Block & Sully ( Jesse Block and Eva Sully (Block)) (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Blondell, Joan (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Bloolips (P.G. "Bette" Bourne, Danny "Diva Dan" Barratt, Vincent "Lavinia Coop" Fox, Paul "Precious Pearl" Shaw, etc.) (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Bolger, Ray (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Bigger, Laura (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Bondi, Beulah (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Bowers, Cookie (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Brachetti, Arturo (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - El Brendel (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Brice, Fanny (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Bronson, Charles (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Brown, Buster (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Brown, George (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Brown, Joe E. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Bubbles, John (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Buckley, Dick (Lord Buckley) (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Bufalino, Brenda (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Burns & Allen ( George Burns and Gracie Allen) (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Butterbeans and Susie ( Jodie Edwards and Susie Hawthorne-Edwards) (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Buttons, Red (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Performers C - D
    - Caesar, Sid (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Cagney, James (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Calloway, Cab (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Calvert, John (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Canova, Judy (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Cantor, Eddie (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Carl Freed's Harmonic Harlequins (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Carle, Richard (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Carlin, George (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Carmichael, Hoagy (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Carpenter, Thelma (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Carus, Emma (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Cavanaugh, Hobart (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Chang, Anna (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Chaplin, Charlie, (see also: Reeves, Alf and Billy) (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Chaplin, Sydney (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Chase, Chaz (Chaz Chase) (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Chase, Charley (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Chevalier, Albert (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Chevalier, Maurice (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Cirque de Sade ( Stephanie Monseu and Keith Nelson) (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Claire, Ina (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Clark, Bobby (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Clayton, Ethel (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Clinger, Will (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Coca, Imogene (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Cohen, Myron (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Cole & Johnson ( Bob Cole and J. Rosamond Johnson; and James Weldon Johnson) (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Collier, William(William, Sr. and William, Jr.) (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Collins, José (Josephine) (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Connor, Chris (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Cook, Joe (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Cooper, Gary (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Cornell, Katherine (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Covan, Willie (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Crabtree, Lotta (Lotta La Petite; Little Lotta) (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Curran, Sean ( Sean Curran Company) (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Dailey, Peter F. (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - D'Arville, Camille (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Davenport Sisters (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Davis, Joan, and Haley, Jack (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Davis, Sammy, Jr. (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - DeMarco, Tony, and DeMarco, Sally (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Deslys, Gaby (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Douglas, Melvyn (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Doyle, Patsy (Patrick) (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Draper, Paul (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Draper, Ruth (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Dressler, Marie (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Duffy, Patrick ( Marlo & Duffy) (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Dumont, Margaret (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Duncan Sisters ( Rosetta Duncan and Vivian Duncan) (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Duo Arnedis ( Arne Ellingstad and Marina Ellingstad) (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Durante, Jimmy (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Performers E - Go
    - Eddie & Lorraine (The Aristocrats of Tiny Wheels) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Edwards, Cliff (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Edwards, Gus (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Elen, Gus (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Ellington, Duke (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Elliott, G.H. (George Henry) (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Elton, Lily (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Emery, Winifred (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Fagan, Noodles, and Fagan, Paxton (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Farrar, Geraldine (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Farrell, Eileen (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Fernandel ( Fernand-Joseph-Désiré Contandin) (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Fetchit, Stepin ( Lincoln Perry) (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Fields, Gracie (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Fink's Mules (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Fitzgerald, Ella (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Flagstad, Kirsten (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Flavin, Margaret ( Margaret Flavin Sheehan), and Watson, Billy (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Fletcher, Dusty (Clinton Fletcher, 1897-1954) (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Flippen, Jay C. (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Foley, Joe, and Kenney, Joseph (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Ford Sisters ( Dora Ford and Mabel Ford) (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Forde, Florrie (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Four Step Brothers ( Maceo Anderson, Al Williams, Red Walker, Sherman Robertson) (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Fox, Della (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Foy, Eddie (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Friganza, Trixie (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Frost & Morrison (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Gartelle Brothers (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Genée, Adelina (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Gilbert, William Schwenck (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Gilder, George (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Gillette, William (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Gilmore, Charles "Mike" (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Gilson, Lottie (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Glose, Augusta (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Glover, Savion (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Goodner, Lillian (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Goodwin, Nat (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Gordon, Bert (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Gordon, Ruth (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Performers Gr - J
    - Betty Grable (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Le Grand David (magic show) (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - The Great Raymond ( Maurice Saunders) (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Great Small Works (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Green, Mitzi (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Greenwood, Charlotte (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Grey & Byron ( Mildred "Dolly" Grey and Bert Byron) (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Grey, Lizzie/Lissie (Lizzie/Lissie Gray; Elizabeth (Ganssler) Wilson) (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Grock ( Charles Adrien Wettach) (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Guilbert, Yvette (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Hall, Adelaide (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Harmonica Rascals ( Borrah Minevitch) (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Harper, Leonard (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Harrigan & Hart ( Edward "Ned" Harrigan and Tony Hart) (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Harris, Julie (correspondence) (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Harry, Deborah, and McGill, Everett (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Havoc, June (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Henlere, Herschel (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Hindu Belles (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Hines, Gregory (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Hitchcock, Raymond (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Hoen, Max, Cora, and Ed (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Hoffmann, Gertrude (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Holiday, Billie, and Armstrong, Louis (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Hope, Bob (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Houdini, Harry (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Howard, Willie, and Howard, Eugene (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Humes, Helen (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Hunter, Alberta (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Huntington, Agnes (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Hutton, Betty (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - International Sweethearts of Rhythm (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Irving, Henry, Sir (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Irwin, Bill (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Ito, Michio (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Janis, Elsie (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Jefferson, Joe (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Johns, Brooke (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Johnstone, Sibyl (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Jolson, Al (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Joy, Leatrice (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Performers K - Man
    - Kaye, Danny (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Karamazov Brothers (aka: The Flying Karamazov Brothers) (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Keaton, Buster, (see also: The Keaton Chronicle, in Periodicals) (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Kelly & Galvin ( Phil Kelly and Joe Galvin - The Actor & The Italian) (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Kelly, J.W. (Rolling Mill Man) (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Kelly, Patsy (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - King, Hetty (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Kitt, Eartha (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Lackaye, Wilton (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Lahr, Bert (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Lamarr, Hedy (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Langdon, Harry, (see also: Wild About Harry, in Periodicals) (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Las-Cellas, Sarah (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Laurel & Hardy ( Stan Laurel and Oliver Hardy) (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Lavelle - Ross (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Lea, Barbara (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Leguizamo, John (Mambo King of Comedy) (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Leno, Dan (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Lenya, Lotte (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Leonar, Eddie (Our Minstrel) (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - LeRoy, Hal (CIGAR) (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Lewis, Furry ( Walter E. Lewis) (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Lillie, Beatrice (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Limón, José (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Lindfors, Viveca (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Lippman, Walter (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Little Tich (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Lloyd, Alice (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Lloyd, Harold (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Loftus, Cecilia, and Loftus, Marie (mother) (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Low, Rowland (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Loy, Myrna (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Lugosi, Bela (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Luke, Keye, and Robert Ito (with Chet Dowling) (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Lyons, Carnell (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Mack, Frank Guy (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Mack, Ollie (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Mackenzie, Mary (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Mahoney, Will, and Maria Elena (daughter; painter) (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Makishi, Stacy (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Mankin, Harley (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Mantell, Anna (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Performers Marx - N
    - Marx Brothers ( Harpo Marx, Groucho Marx, and Chico Marx) (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - McIntyre, Heath (James McIntrye and Thomas K. Heath) (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - McNulty, Jennie (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - McRae, Carmen (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Menes, Michael (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Midler, Bette (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Mignon ( Sadie Rosenberg) (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Miller, Ann (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Mills, Florence (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Miss Broadway (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Mr. Nostalgia ( Bob Cusack) (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Mr. Slim's Goodtime Ragtime Vaudeville Revival ( R.W. Bacon and L.J. Newton) (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Mitchell and Durant ( Frank Mitchell and Jack Durant) (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Monty Python ( John Cleese) (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Moore, Marianne (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Moore, Tom (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Moran and Mack ( George Moran and Charlie Mack - "The Two Black Crows") (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Moran, Polly (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Moreland, Mantan (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Morlacchi, Giuseppina, and Texas Jack (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Morse, Lee (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Morton, Jelly Roll (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Murray, Ken (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Napier, Valantyne, and Napier, Hector (father) (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Neagle, Anna (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Negri, Pola (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Neilson, Julia (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Newhart, Bob (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Newton-John, Olivia (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Nicholas Brothers ( Fayard Nicholas and Harold Nicholas) (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Noble, Venza, and Ogden, Margie, (Note: there is a single photo of this duo; contains primarily photos of other entertainers, most autographed to Venza Noble, also spelled Noblet, Noblett or Noblette.) (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Norman, Mary, and Norman, Ron (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Performers O - R
    - Oakley, Annie (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - O'Brien, Pat (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - O'Day, Anita (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Oliver Band (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Oliver, Richard (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Olivier, Laurence (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Palace Music Hall Girls (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Patton, Frank (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Pavlova, Anna, and Mordkin, Mikhail (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - The Payton Trio (Lew, Hattie, and Clifton) (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Peters Sisters (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Piaf, Edith (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Pickford, Mary (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Pitts, ZaSu (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Pollard, Daphne, and Stanley, Katherine (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Potts, Ernie, & Company (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Powell, Eleanor (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Raft, George (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Rainey, Ma (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Rand, Sally (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Ravel Troupe (François, Gabriel, Jean, and others) (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Raye, Martha (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Reed Sisters ( Melva Reed and Bonnie Reed) (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Reeves, Al (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Reeves, Alf, and Reeves, Billy (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Renault, Francis (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Rice, Fanny (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Richman, Harry (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Ring, Blanche (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Rio Brothers (Ed and Joe) (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Ritz Brothers (Stage names: Al, Jimmy and Harry; given names Abraham, Samuel and Herschel Joachim) (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Roach, Hal (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Robert, Joe (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Robeson, Paul (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Robey, George (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Robins, Adolph (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Robinson, Bill (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Robinson, John - John Robinson's Circus (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Rogers Brothers (Stage names: Max and Gus Rogers; given names Max and Gus Soloman) ( Joe Weber and Lew Fields), (see also: Weber and Fields) (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Rogers, Will (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Rose Marie (Guy) (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Ross and Fenton ( Charles J. Ross and Mabel Fenton) (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Ross, Hope (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Roventini, Johnny (Philip Morris bellboy) (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Rowland, Adele (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Royal Rockets (John Carson, Dorothy Carson Smidt and Paul Smidt) (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Royal Tokyo Japanese Troupe (circa 1910) (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Rubin, Benny (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Rubinstein, Arthur (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Russell, Jane (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Russell, Lillian (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Performers S - T
    - Samuels, Rae (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Santoro, Margaret (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Savo, Jimmy (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Scheerer, Robert (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Seeley, Blossom, and Fields, Benny (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Semon, Larry (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Short, Bobby (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Sidney, Sylvia (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Skinner, Otis (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Slate Brothers (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Smith, Bessie (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Joe, and Bale, Chas (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Smith, Kate (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Smith, Maggie (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Spacek, Sissy, and Roberts, Eric (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Sparks, Ned (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - St. Denis, Ruth, and Shawn, Ted, (see also: Photographs, Box 22) (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Stathos, Margaret Moreland (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Storch, Larry (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Stritch, Elaine (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Suratt, Valeska (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Swanson, Gloria (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Tabor, Baby Doe ( Elizabeth McCourt Tabor) (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Talma, LeRoy, and Bosco, Mirth (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Tan, Margaret Leng (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Tanguay, Eva (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Tempest, Marie (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Templeton, Fay (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Thompson, Lydia (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Three Musical Moods (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - The Three Stooges ( Larry Fine, Moe Howard, and Joe DiRita) (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Three X Sisters (Hamilton Sisters and Fordyce; Pearl Santos, Vi Hamilton, and Jessie Fordyce) (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Tilly, Vesta (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Tip, Tap & Toe (Ray Winfield (leader) with Samuel Green, Ted Fraser and Freddie James) (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Tormé, Mel (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Tracy, Arthur (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Tucker, Sophie (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Travato (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Tully, May (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Turpin, Ben (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Performers U - W
    - Unidentified (various) (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Urline, Capitola (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Valaida, Snow (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Van, Billy B. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Vance, Clarice (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Vardon & Perry ( Frank A. Vardon and Harry H. Perry) (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Vaughan, Sarah (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - The Vents (Ruth and Ray) (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Vesta Victoria ( Victoria Lawrence) (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Vidor, King (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Walking Brothers (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Warfield, David (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Washington, Dinah (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Waters, Doris and Waters, Elsie (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Watson, Billy (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Watson Sisters (Fanny and Kitty) (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Wayburn, Ned (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Weber, Joe, and Fields, Lew (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Weeks, Larry (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Weill, Kurt (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Welles, Orson ( Citizen Kane) (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Westfield, Catherine (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Wethersby, Emma (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Wheeler & Woolsey ( Bert Wheeler and Robert Woolsey - Mummy's Boys, 1936) (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Whiting, Margaret (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Wiere Brothers ( Harry Wiere, Herbert Wiere, and Sylvester Wiere) (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Williams, Herb (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Williams, Joe (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Williams, Marion (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Wilson, Wesley (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Performers (oversize)
    - Dardanelle ( Dardanelle Hadley) (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Fanchon & Marco ( Fanny Wolff and Mike Wolff) (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Fields, W.C. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Frost and Morrison (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Gielgud, John, Sir (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Gish, Lillian (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Graham, Martha (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Horne, Rudy (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Valliere, Geraldine (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Waters, Ethel (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Weber, Joe (and Lew Fields) (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - West, Mae (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Wynn, Ed (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Zaloom, Paul (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Series V: Obituaries, .25 linear foot
  This series consists of newspaper clippings of obituaries, many of them originally glued onto scrapbook pages; they are generally provided as photocopies. They are organized alphabetically by surname or stage name. The subjects include a broad range of singers, dancers, actors, comedians, and other personalities, including some outside the realm of entertainment.
  Obituaries are also located in the Performers files, when there is other material about that performer.
  - Obituaries A - C (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Abbott, George
    Alinsky, Saul
    Allen, Dayton
    Anderson, Maceo
    Atkins, Cholly (Charles)
    Barnes, Binnie ( Gittel Enoyce)
    Bates, Clayton (Peg Leg Bates)
    Bird, Billie ( Billie Bird Sellen)
    Bogue, Merwyn
    Borge, Victor
    Bricktop ( Ada Beatrice Queen Victoria Louise Virginia Smith)
    Brown, Johnny Mack
    Bruce, Lenny
    Cage, John
    Carney, Art
    Churchill, Marguerite
    Clyde, Andy
    Coogan, Jackie
    Cook, Elisha
    Corio, Ann
    Cornell, Katharine
    Cotten, Elizabeth
    Crawford, Joan
    Cronyn, Hume
    Cukor, George
    Cummings, Constance
    Cunningham, Merce
  - Obituaries D - F (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Dale, Charles (of Joe Smith and Charlie Dale)
    Daniels, Bebe (Phyllis)
    Darwell, Jane
    Dawn, Dolly ( Theresa Maria Stabile)
    Delmar, Kenny
    Devine, Andy
    Dietz, Howard
    Dooley, Ray ( Rachel Rice Dooley)
    Douglas, Helen Gahagan
    Douglas, William O.
    Dove, Billie ( Lillian Bohny)
    Downey, Morton
    Dresser, Louise
    Farina, Richard
    Farlow, Talmage "Tal" Holt
    Farrell, Glenda
    Fealy, Maude
    Feldman, Marty
  - Obituaries G - I (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Gardiner, Reginald
    George, Dan, Chief ( Geswanouth Slahoot)
    Gingold, Hermione
    Gish, Dorothy
    Goman, Charles Raymond
    Goodman, Ace ( Goodman Aiskowitz)
    Gorcey, Leo
    Gosden, Freeman (of "Amos 'n' Andy")
    Griffith, Corinne
    Guinness, Alec
    Hairston, Jester
    Haley, Jack
    Halop, Billy
    Hammond, John
    Haney, Carol
    Harding, Ann
    Hawthorne, Nigel
    Hayes, Roland
    Hickson, Joan
    Hildegarde ( Hildegarde Loretta Sell)
    Homolka, Oscar
    Hopkins, Miriam
    Hughes, Russell Meriweather
    Hulbert, Jack
    Huntz, Hall
  - Obituaries J - L (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Jackson, Eddie (of Clayton, Jackson and Durante)
    Jaffe, Sam
    Jenkins, Allen
    Johnson, Nunnally
    Kane, Helen
    Keeler, Ruby
    Keller, Greta
    Kelly, Emmett
    Kelly, Fred
    Koestler, Arthur
    Laye, Evelyn
    Le Gallienne, Eva
    Lindquist, John
    Loudon, Dorothy
    Lukas, Paul
    Lunt, Alfred
    Lupescu, Magda (Elena)
  - Obituaries M - P (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Maracci, Carmelita
    Mason, James
    Matthau, Walter
    Mayo, Virginia
    McHugh, Frank
    Mercer, Johnny
    Merman, Ethel
    Miscellaneous from Variety ( Buddy Rogers, Ellen Corby, Señor Wences, L.C. "Speedy" Huggins)
    Mitchell, Jimmy "Sir Slyde" ( James Titus Godbolt)
    Monk, Thelonious
    Moore, Dudley
    Morley, Robert
    Morse, Ella Mae
    Murray, Mae
    Nelson, Portia
    Nesbitt, Cathleen
    Nielsen, Asta
    Oakie, Jack
    Parker, Dorothy
    Pollard, Harry (Keystone Kop)
    Powell, William
  - Obituaries Q - S (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Quayle, Anthony, Sir
    Rambova, Natacha (second wife of Rudolph Valentino)
    Reed, Leonard
    Renoir, Jean
    Richardson, Ralph
    Ritchard, Cyril
    Ritter, Thelma
    Rogers, Ginger
    Roth, Lillian
    Russell, Nipsy
    Rutherford, Maude
    Ryan, Peggy (Margaret O'Rene)
    Scott, Hazel D.
    Señor Wences ( Wenceslao Moreño)
    Sheridan, Ann
    Simone, Nina
    Sokolow, Anna
    Stevenson, Adlai
    Strauss, Robert
    Syms, Sylvia
  - Obituaries T - Z (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Trevor, Claire
    Turner, Daisy
    Ulanova, Galina
    Valois, Ninette de
    Ward, Aida
    Warren, Earl
    Webb, Clifton
    Welch, Elisabeth
    Wilder, Billy
    Wilder, Marshall P.
    Wiley, Lee
    Williams, Marion
    Wilson, Edith (Aunt Jemima)
    Winwood, Estelle
    Wray, Fay
    Wright, Richard
    Young, Gig ( Byron Elsworth Barr)
    Young, Loretta (Gretchen)
- Series VI: Theatres, ca. 1894-2007, 1.5 linear feet
  This series encompasses four subseries:
  Subseries 1: Theatre Postcards, Photographs, and Ephemera, ca. 1894-2004
  Subseries 2: Theatre Programs, 1892-2007
  Subseries 3: Souvenir Programs, 1899-ca. 2003
  Subseries 4: Boston Theatre Programs, ca. 1920-1952
  - Subseries 1: Theatre Postcards, Photographs, and Ephemera, ca. 1894-2004
    This subseries consists primarily of postcards depicting entertainment theatre buildings, mostly in the United States. Other materials include admission tickets, announcements, photographs, and commemorative booklets. There are a few postcards of non-theatre subjects. The series is organized alphabetically by state, with a miscellaneous grouping at the end.
    - California (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Fox Theatre (San Francisco, Calif.) - photograph
      Movieland Wax Museum (Buena Park, Calif.)
      Orpheum Theatre (San Francisco, Calif.)
    - Illinois (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Gaiety Theatre (Galesburg, Ill.)
      Majestic Theatre (Chicago, Ill.)
      Maxwell Street Market (Chicago, Ill.)
      Orpheum Theatre (Chicago, Ill.)
      Rialto Theatre (Chicago, Ill.) - miniature program